P.DAMIEN MURINDANGABO CYUZUZO

Software engineer





31.07.1991



0785485889

zudanga@gmail.com

SOCIAL MEDIA



in linkedin.com/in/pierre-damien-murindangabo-cyuzuzo-709b53151/

PROFILE

Software Engineer with 4+ years of experience developing different online platform. having skills with MSQL database. Languages: PHP, SQL, typescript, and javascript

Opensource: Rabbit MQ, XMPP protocols, OpenStreetMap Frontend framework: AngularJs, Angular and React

Backend framework: Slim-PHP, Java Environement: google cloud (qcp) and amazon web services (aws)Software

EDUCATION

2011 - 2015

Bachelor of Science (Hons), Engineering

(COMPUTER ENGINEERING)

National Univeristy of Rwanda (former KIST) computer engineering and information technology

EXPERIENCE

07.2018

DMM.НеНе

Senior software developer

Responsibilities: Update and create new features in all the system the company is rolling out. and Building reusable code and libraries for future use. skills gained in this position include

XMPP protocols, rabitMq service, Angular 6, typescript and ReactJs

03.2017 - 07.2018

DMM.НеНе

Software Engineer

Responsibilities: Integration of user-facing from front-end with server-side web services, skills gained on this position include using OpenStreetMap service.

03.2016 - 02.2017

HeHelabs Itd

junior software developer

Responsibilities: Contributing to the development of high-level system design diagrams, coding, testing, debugging, deployment and documentation skills gained in this position include JavaScript and AngularJs.

06.2016 - 02.2017

BAHO INTERNATIONAL HOSPITAL

Software Developer

Responsibilities: Update and maintenance of OpenMr project (system to manage the hospital in general)Maintain hospital data, Help and train doctors and patients to the system. skills gained include PHP and database management.

07.2013 - 08.2014

National Bank of Rwanda

intern

skills gained include Networking, Configuration of IP-Phone



SKILLS

✓ Front-End Development

(Native javascript, ReactJs, angularJs, angular 6)

- ✓ Back-End Development (java spring MVC,slim 2 php,sql)
- ✓ Computer environment

 linux(ubuntu,fedora),windows(xp,7,8,10)

PERSONALITY

✓ Communicative

✓ Punctuality

✓ Creativity

✓ Organized

HOBBY

Aerobic exercise, reading tech books, movies and tv show, reality television

LANGUAGES

English

French • • • • •

REFEREES

- Clarisse Iribagiza CEO of DMM.HeHe
- **Dr.Donart Dr.NGARAMBE** Vice-Dean of school of ICT in UR-CST
- **Dr.Bajpai GAURAV** Head of Computer and software engineering Department in UR-CST

